Hugh Duong-Tran-Tien

45 Lilac Street, Inala, Brisbane, QLD 4077 0422113629

hugh.dtt@gmail.com | https://hughdtt.gitlab.io/personal-website/ https://gitlab.com/hughdtt | https://www.linkedin.com/in/hugh-duong-tran-tien-12227b911a

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Efficient Student pursuing Information Technology degree with experience collaborating with teammates to create high quality and maintainable products. Well-versed in problem solving with strong understanding of programming principles. Willing to learn new skills and confident in self-teaching.

EDUCATION

Queensland University of Technology

02/2016 - 11/2021 (Expected)

Brisbane, QLD

Bachelor of Information Technology/ Bachelor of Laws (Honours)

- Majoring in Computer Science
- Coursework in Algorithms and Complexity, Web Development and Project Design/Development.

SKILLS

Languages

- Proficient in: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Java, C#
- Familiar in: Python, Node

Software

- Database Management: Experience in MySQL, PostgreSQL, Dbeaver
- Platforms: Proficient in Microsoft Windows 10 Development
- Frameworks: Experience in **Django, Bootstrap**
- Project Development: Proficient in Agile, SCRUM and Git

EXPERIENCE

Student Intern 03/2019 – 11/2019

Arq Group, Brisbane City, QLD

- As a team member designed, built and maintained a Slack Chatbot application using Node SDK and Slack API.
- Used database tools **PostgreSQL** and **Dbeaver**.

Tutorial Assistant 01/2017 – 01/2019

Kumon Forest Lake Education Centre, Forest Lake, QLD

- Collaborated with students to complete homework tasks, identified lagging skills and corrected weaknesses.
- Motivated students towards learning and studying to build self-confidence and reduce anxiety of failure.
- Worked well with both students and staff in a classroom environment to provide educational support.

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

Leader-In-Training

01/2016-06/2018

Vietnamese Eucharistic Youth Movement, Inala, QLD

- Participated in organizing social events.
- Aided in teaching classes.
- Developed leadership and communication skills.

REFEREES

Available upon request.